So, Sir, if you want to invest in ICICI Loard,
or if you have
stock in this company,
what should you do?
Look, Sir, first of all, I would like to give you
a disclaimer. I
also have a personal investment in this company. So, it's not like
I'm telling you to
buy it because you have to. This was a
disclaimer. After that, I would like to tell you,
Sir, this company will become a company that you could
n't imagine could become so big. So,
if you look at general insurance
companies in India,
I'm talking about private insurance
companies.
In general insurance, it is the leader. And if you
look at it, its growth is better than the government companies. So,
you're not alone in thinking of buying this company.
Sir, many people have invested
money here.
And if you look at the stock price, you'll see it's
currently 1004.8. The
stock is trading above its lifetime high. Even then, I
can tell you with certainty that Sir,
you'll see this stock going higher.
How high?  This is not my opinion Sir, how
high can it go, I would
like to show you the target of a brokerage firm Jafferys here and
what target has it set, so Sir, what is the
target set by Jafferys for ICC Lord's stock
here, assuming this,
if you see, what was the target price
earlier, it used to be
₹570, how much has it increased from that to ₹
1630, so he has mentioned the buy rating here
and if you see the
growth, that is, the growth of 13 per cent,
if you see the profit,
you will see the profit of almost 17 per cent here, so
Sir, I mean, what I feel is that
this company can give you explosive returns, which is
called explosive returns,
and from 2017 to 2020,
if you calculate the 3-year return here, then
Sir, you will see here in front of your screen that the
company has given a return of 115 per cent in 3 years.  I have
made it and given it to you Sir and how much do you want,
what do you mean in 3 years, I mean in 3 years, will I give
300, 400, 500, 600, yes, there is no such
thing that I will not be able to give it, Sir, but I mean, I am
afraid of those companies which give very high, very high, which means unexpected returns, Sir, I would
like to tell you Sir, I am
afraid of those returns, yes, if you
see the returns, these are the returns made in the stock market,
Sir, a good company like
Reliance has made it and given it, if you see, in 1 year, it has
earned a return of around 80%, Sir, so
Sir, it is not that it cannot make these returns,
big companies cannot run and
cannot beat the high for a lifetime, these are some
myths which you have to keep in your mind here,
but if you remain adamant on that,
this company has made its high
and after this it will come down, after that it will go up
again, after that it will increase by ₹10 and will go
down, Sir, if you keep on believing such myths, then
Sir, you will miss investing in a good company,
if you buy the
stock of such lords  If you want to take it, then note down today's date
here, sir. On November 26,
2020, No About Investment is telling you
that after 2 years, your stock will be around this price, which means
you will not even be able to imagine, it can give such
returns, sir, if you
look at the insurance penetration in India,
sir, what is it, what is it, what is it, sir,
if you see, sir, you will see that the demand for insurance is
picking
up, there will be a storm gaining momentum, people will do insurance here in abundance, and about such nonsense, if you do not know yet, have not read it, have not completed your research yet, then to make your research easier for you, sir, I would like to tell you that I have
made an excellent video of separate fundamental analysis on this, I will
give its link in the description, please
go and watch that video once
and you will know, sir,
here Jafferis, you have already seen what a
target is, but
sir, he has kept an expectation
that it can give, but sir, if you
see, if this  Returns: They can go even above this, they
can increase their target price further. Yes, you should
n't forget the downside as well, but
sir, what I feel is that the downside is
limited here, it's very limited.
Here, you will see the stock falling.
In a falling market, ICC World's
stock should be added to your portfolio.
Sir, this is the strategy you have to adopt. Otherwise,
sir, I keep telling you again and again, sir, I am saying this, that's why
you should not invest. You have to
read it a thousand times at least before investing.
You will see many stocks in the market right now,
which you will see hitting the upper circuit every day.
You are thinking of
buying them, buying them, but sir, it does
n't take long for money to sink.
If you don't know about Lakshmi Vilas Bank, if
you used to have that bank's stock,
its value has reached zero. Sir, it has reached
zero. So,
please don't invest in such a company, which, if you
see here, could be over in a day or two. So, do
n't invest in such a company. There are
very good, fundamentally strong companies in the stock market
where you can invest.  You should keep
looking for opportunities. Rest Sir,
please do tell us by commenting how you liked the video. If you have
not subscribed to the channel yet, then do subscribe to the channel
and do not forget to tell us how you liked this video by
liking or disliking it.
Thank you, Jai Hind.